<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:iweb="http://www.apple.com/iweb" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>The ITK Blog</title>
    <link>http://www.itkinfo.com/ITK/Blog/Blog.html</link>
    <description> </description>
    <generator>iWeb 3.0.1</generator>
    <item>
      <title>How it all began</title>
      <link>http://www.itkinfo.com/ITK/Blog/Entries/2010/3/3_How_it_all_began.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">97b438e7-bbc3-41ba-8f51-d9d58ef021d7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 3 Mar 2010 11:45:11 -0800</pubDate>
      <description>First off - I have to start by saying that I’m uncomfortable with this whole thing.   I’m a very private person.   I never update my status on Facebook.   I spent an entire shower thinking about clever status updates but never felt like I had anything worth broadcasting to the 200 people that I’m ‘Friends’ with.   &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So the idea of sharing my thoughts and experiences - not in a controlled one on one in person interaction but with unseen and people is not something I’m particularly eager to do.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;And yet. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Here we are.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Maybe it’s because I have time to think while feeding my new baby.  Thinking about wanting to share with him.   To teach him. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Or because I really want to make something of this accidental business (much more on that to follow if I keep this up).  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Either way.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Here I am.   I imagine that this will be a place for me to write about several things.   How my business got started, where I’d like it to go, what I’m trying to do to get it there, and sharing interesting reading that I come across on my journey.  &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Thanks for reading, stranger.   For now - since I’m using IWeb and not going through a Mobileme account I can’t allow comments on here.   Feel free to email me if there’s anything you care to share. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
